const data = [     
    {
    product_id: 1,
    licence_name: "Pokemon",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Pidgeotto",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    product_price: 1799.99,
    dues: 10,
    product_sku: "PKM001001",
    img_front: "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 2,
    licence_name: "Pokemon",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Charmander",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    product_price: 2299.99,
    dues: 6,
    product_sku: "PKM001002",
    img_front: "/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 3,
    licence_name: "Pokemon",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Pikachu",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    product_price: 2699.99,
    dues: 12,
    product_sku: "PKM001003",
    img_front: "/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 4,
    licence_name: "Pokemon",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Vulpix",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    product_price: 2799.99,
    dues: 9,
    product_sku: "PKM001004",
    img_front: "/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 5,
    licence_name: "Harry Potter",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Harry Potter",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    product_price: 2399.99,
    dues: 6,
    product_sku: "HP001005",
    img_front: "/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 6,
    licence_name: "Harry Potter",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Hermione Granger",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    product_price: 2399.99,
    dues: 6,
    product_sku: "HP001006",
    img_front: "/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 7,
    licence_name: "Harry Potter",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Luna Lovegood Lionmask",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    product_price: 1999.99,
    dues: 3,
    product_sku: "HP001007",
    img_front: "/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 8,
    licence_name: "Star Wars",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Baby Yoda",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    product_price: 1799.99,
    dues: 10,
    product_sku: "SW001008",
    img_front: "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 9,
    licence_name: "Star Wars",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Bobbafeth",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    product_price: 1799.99,
    dues: 10,
    product_sku: "SW001009",
    img_front: "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp"
    },
    {
    product_id: 10,
    licence_name: "Star Wars",
    category_name: "Figuras coleccionables",
    product_name: "Stormtrooper",
    product_description: "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    product_price: 1799.99,
    dues: 10,
    product_sku: "SW001010",
    img_front: "/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
    img_back: "/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"
    },
]

module.exports = data;